clubthrifty.com 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use | Club Thrifty

Club Thrifty Media, LLC is very concerned about the privacy of your information. Below is our “Privacy Policy” and “Terms of Use.”

Last modified: May 24, 2018

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, State of Residence or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To present our site and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information about your newsletter subscription.
  * To carry out, evaluate and improve our business (which may include sharing your information with our agents and third-party service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf, such as data analytics, developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications).
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features.
  * To send periodic emails or other forms of contact regarding orders you have submitted, products/services/events we believe may interest you, periodic newsletters to which you may have subscribed, and information about those newsletters.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
  * To provide or refer you to specific products or services that you specifically request from us.
  * To notify you about changes to our site.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our site.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

You may opt out of email communications from us at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button in the email. We will not share your email address with any third parties unless you direct us to do so. If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
An external PCI compliant payment gateway handles all CC transactions.  
We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**  
**•**  Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.  
**•**  Keep track of and serve advertisements.  
**•**  Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

 **If users disable cookies in their browser:**  
If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site.

 **Third-party disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies and terms of use (see below), or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third-party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**  
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the [DART cookie](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

 **We have implemented the following:**  
• Remarketing with Google AdSense

• Google Display Network Impression Reporting

• Demographics and Interests Reporting

• DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Controlling Your Information and Opting out:**  
Google is restricted in its ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **Advertising Privacy Statement**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

 **For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

 **Opting out of Internet Based  Advertising (IBA):**  
You may control your personal information and advertising choices at [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/). You may also opt out of receiving IBA from many sites by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”) at the [DAA consumer choice service](http://www.aboutads.info/) and the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) at the [NAI Service](https://www.networkadvertising.org/). Please note that all tools provided at the [DAA opt-out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) and  [NAI opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) are provided by third parties, not Club Thrifty.

As a courtesy, opt-out links for other third-party services we may use are listed below. Please note that opting out may mean you receive an “opt-out” cookie. This helps networks understand not to assign you new cookies moving forward. Although you will continue to be served ads, these ads are not targeted by your online behaviors. Erasing your browser cookies may require you to complete this process again. Note that these opt-out programs and options are are controlled by third parties. Club Thrifty is not responsible for the accuracy of any claims regarding these programs or for their effectiveness and/or compliance.

Alexa                            [Opt-Out Link](https://support.alexa.com/hc/en-us/articles/200685410-Opting-Out-of-Alexa-Measurement-Pixel)

Double Click               [Opt-Out Link](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)

Facebook                     [Opt-Out Link](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Google                          [Opt-Out Link](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Google Analytics        [Opt-Out Link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Google Retargeting   [Opt-Out Link](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)

Parsley                         [Opt-Out Link](http://srv.config.parsely.com/optout)

Piwik                            [Opt-Out Link](https://piwik.org/privacy/)

Scorecardresearch    [Opt-Out Link](http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx) 

Taboola                        [Opt-Out Link](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy) 

Quantcast                    [Opt-Out Link](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/)

Yahoo                           [Opt-Out Link](https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/index.htm) 

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act**  
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**  
Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or, at a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.  
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

You can change your personal information:

  * By emailing us

 **How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**  
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

 **Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  
It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**  
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old and do not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age on this site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we are happy to delete that information. Please contact us at info@clubthrifty.com with concerns.

 **Fair Information Practices**  
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**  
We will notify you via email:  
**•**  Within 7 business days

We will notify the users via in-site notification  
**•**  Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**  
**•**  Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
**•**  Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
**•**  Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
**•**  Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
**•**  Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
**•**  Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

 **If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can:**  
**•**  Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.

 **Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

  * Access your personal data
  * Ensure the accuracy of your personal data
  * The right to have us delete your personal data
  * The right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and
  * The right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us using the contact information found below.

 **Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Club Thrifty Media, LLC  
P.O. Box 6240, Noblesville, IN 46060  
USA  
info@clubtrifty.com

## Terms of Use

 **Use of Email**  
Any emails sent to Club Thrifty are considered to be property of Club Thrifty Media, LLC. Please be aware that your tips or questions may be published on the website, though we will refrain from posting personally identifiable information.

 **Use of Comments**  
This site permits readers to leave comments expressing their views about the articles published on Club Thrifty. However, you are solely responsible for the materials you post here. By using Club Thrifty, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless this website and its agents with respect to any claims based upon the transmission of your messages.

We are not responsible for the the accuracy or usefulness of any information posted, nor do we warrant or vouch for the contents of any message. Comments express the views of the author of the message only. Comments do not reflect the opinions of this website’s administrators or bloggers.

Comments, responses, and other user-generated content is not provided or commissioned by this site or our advertisers. Responses have not been reviewed, approved or otherwise endorsed by this website or our advertisers. It is not the responsibility of our advertisers or this website to ensure that all comments and/or questions are answered.

If you chose to leave a comment, you agree to keep your comments:

  * relevant to the topic
  * respectful of others, and
  * suitable for a family forum

You shall refrain from posting any material that:

  * is abusive
  * contains knowingly false statements, libel, or slander
  * infringes upon the copyright, trademark, or other intellectual property of others
  * contains excessive use of foul language (note excessive)
  * contains references to adult content
  * contains spam or unwanted commercial solicitations
  * violates any laws or legal rights of other persons or entities

Comments appear in real-time making it is impossible for us to review every message immediately. We do not actively monitor the contents of this website and are not responsible for any messages posted. However, if we are made aware of a violation of our terms of use, we will remove the offending comments immediately without warning. We reserve the right to ban repeat offenders from the website, permanently.

Additionally, the following policy applies to all comments on Club Thrifty:

  *     * By posting a comment, you grant us the right to use, display, republish, sell, alter, or delete your comment in any way and for any reason.
    * You, the author, may not edit or remove your comments once they are posted. Furthermore, it is not our responsibility or duty to delete or edit your comment in any way at your request; however, we do reserve the right to edit your comment at our complete discretion.
    * This policy is subject to change at any time without notice.
    * Unsolicited commercial comments are not allowed.
